Cunard Lines
Marist College
Cunard Lines
1789 1984
Marist Archives and Special Collections 3399 North Road, Poughkeepsie, New York 12601
Lowell Thomas
2.1.1.1.5
1203 linear feet
Items in this collection do not circulate and may be used in-house only.
- Lowell Thomas Papers
  - Graphic Materials, 2
    - Photographs, 2.1
      - Glass Plate Negatives, 2.1.1
        - Frank R. Roberson, 2.1.1.1
          - Cunard Lines, 2.1.1.1.5
              - Parlor, copy, before 1916; 28 (Box 1177)
                4x5
              - Picture over fireplace, before 1916; 29
              - The Aquitania out of water, before 1916; 30
              - People looking at the propeller of the Aquitinia, before 1916; 31
              - Painting over a table, before 1916; 32
              - Painting over a table, before 1916; 33
              - Looking at propeller of the Aquitania, before 1916; 34
              - Subway train in smokestack of the Aquitania, before 1916; 35
              - The Aquitania out of water, before 1916; 36
              - Hallway of the Aquitania, before 1916; 37
              - View of empty deck, before 1916; 38
              - Small boats next to large ship, before 1916; 39
              - View of Aquitania's propellers, before 1916; 40
              - Table and chairs, before 1916; 41
              - Bedroom, before 1916; 42
              - Ship deck, before 1916; 43
              - Table and foreplace in stateroom, before 1916; 44
              - Swimming pool? on ship, before 1916; 45
              - Lounge, before 1916; 46
              - Small boat on the Aquitania, before 1916; 47
              - Tables and chairs on deck, before 1916; 48
              - Dining room on the Aquitania, before 1916; 49
              - Dining room, before 1916; 50
              - Buildings and smokwstacks, before 1916; 51
              - Ship gymnasium, before 1916; 52
              - Lounge, before 1916; 1 (Box 1178)
              - Lounge, before 1916; 2
              - Top of staircase, before 1916; 3
              - Lifeboats on the Aquitania, before 1916; 4
              - Lounge, before 1916; 5
              - Chairs and tables on ship, before 1916; 6
              - Sitting room, before 1916; 7
              - Dining room, before 1916; 8
              - Sitting room, before 1916; 9
              - Lounge with piano, before 1916; 10
              - Cunard highway, copy, before 1916; 11
              - Following the flag, copy, before 1916; 12
              - Mr. Jones, before 1916; 13
                5x7
              - Mr. Hoblyn, before 1916; 14
              - Purser of the Campania, before 1916; 15
              - Captain at the Cunard Line, before 1916; 16
              - Crowds at the Cunard Lines, before 1916; 17
                film
              - Cunard Line, before 1916; 18